

Profile

I am a full-time freelance web developer who specializes in creating dynamic and beautiful webpages.

I am a team-worker, responsible for his work, creative, attentive, highly expert in the design and a reliable person. I have a skill of solving problems, have confidence in his inteligence, ability and memory.

Contact

Azerbaijan, Sumgait

+994(055)-942-46-14

+994(051)-360-57-31

rizvanyh@code.edu.az

https://github.com/ HaciyevRizvan

Rizvan Hajiyev Web Developer

EDUCATION

Code Academy(Apr - 2017 | Dec - 2017) - Software Development

Azerbaijan University of Languages
(2010 - 2014) - Philology faculty of the English

EXPERIENCE

• 2016-2017 - PROGRAMMER

I have worked on some projects during this period of time. They are:

1.Front-End Works

https://github.com/HaciyevRizvan/SimpleResponsiveWebsite https://github.com/HaciyevRizvan/Final-AntiqueMall https://github.com/HaciyevRizvan/Final-front-template https://github.com/HaciyevRizvan/Petcarepro-first-template https://github.com/HaciyevRizvan/New-Web-Creative-

2.Back-End Works

https://github.com/HaciyevRizvan/AntiqueMall-Backend https://github.com/HaciyevRizvan/Bacend_Final

2014-2016 - ACCOUNTANT

The city of Sumgait - "The Stone Firm".

I had analyzed profits and losses, providing information for this Firm need in order to evaluate how a company is doing over a period of time.

SOFTWARE SKILLS

Azerbaijan

Turkish

HTML/CSS	Angular	
BootStrap	MySql	
Sass	C#	
JavaScript	Asp.Net	
Jquery	Photoshop	
Languages		

English

Russian